

Phone: +82 01025345190 | personal website | LinkedIn | GitHub |

Email: seventeenwxy@dgu.ac.kr

INTRODUCTION

A second-year student doing a Master of Science (M.S.) degree in Artificial Intelligence at Dongguk University (DGU) and dedicated efforts to researching **optimization** and **image generation** in recent years. Obtained Bachelor's degree in Computer Science from a renowned University in China Jiangxi province. Current research focuses on **representation learning based on generative models** (e.g., adversarial autoencoder, VAE) to maximize the mutual information between learned representations and input data while improving inference quality.

EDUCATION

Dongguk University

Master student in Artificial Intelligence(GPA:3.75/4.5)

Xinyu University

Bachelor of Science in Computer Science(GPA:3.5/4)

Seoul, South Korea Sep 2021 – Present

Location: Seoul, South Korea

Xinyu, Jiangxi, China Sep 2017 – Jun 2021

RESEARCHS

Multi-adversarial Autoencoders: Stable, Faster and Self-adaptive Representation Learning (Under Review-ESWA)

Multi-adversarial Autoencoder (MAAE), in which AAE leverages multiple discriminators to enhance adversarial training through ensembled feedback across discriminators. We tackle the problem of Maximizing a variational lower bound with reconstruction and adversarial learning objectives, as in AAE, by exploring the benefit of multiple discriminators used in the standard GAN framework. Preprint version is available at <u>SSRN:4530466</u>

EXPERIENCE

Al Internship

2023.7 - 2023.8 Department of AI, Asleep Company

- · Preprocessed and cleaned the time series data, including handling missing values and noisy data.
- Developed a sleep-stage prediction model for time series data using machine learning techniques.
- Utilized cross-validation techniques to assess the model's performance and fine-tuned hyperparameters to improve accuracy.

Teaching Assistant

2022 - 2023 Dongguk University

- Assisting the instructor in preparing course materials, designing assignments, and grading exams.
- Providing individualized feedback to students and addressing their concerns related to the course content.
- Conducting interactive sessions to reinforce programming concepts and debug errors in the code.

Software Internship

2020 Department of IT, Cindaly Company

- Program the front-end web page according to the requirements of the art department.
- Complete the basic Java-related software coding as required.

HONORS AND REWARDS

- Awarded National Scholarship for pursuing Master in Dongguk University (Korea, 2021)
- Xinyu University- Magna Cum Laude (GPA 3.5/4) for graduation
- ChinaSoft International's Excellence-Cup Excellence Award (2019)
- · Awarded National Scholarship for the entire term graduation (China, 2017)

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Skills : Python, Java, HTML, CSS

Research area: Generative Adversarial Networks, Variational AutoEncoder

Languages : Chinese, English, Korean(Topik 5)